gamer.cash 2017-12-31

# Privacy Policy

**Last updated on June 16, 2016.**

This Privacy Policy has been compiled to better serve those who are concerned with how their 'Personally identifiable information' (PII) is being used online. Please read our Privacy Policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with our Website. This Privacy Policy applies to all visitors, users and others who wish to access, view or use the Website. 

**1\. Personal identification information**

We collect your Personally Identifiable Information, including information that you provide when you register on our Website, access the Website via social networks, or associated services available on our Website, email us or subscribe to our Website newsletters. Personally Identifiable Information, as used in US privacy law and information security, is information that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact, or locate a single person, or to identify an individual in context. 

When registering on our Website, as appropriate, a person may be asked to enter his/her name, email address, physical address and telephone number or other details to help him/her with his/her experience. Also, we may collect and store any Personally Identifiable Information you voluntarily submit on our Website and/or voluntarily provide to us in any other manner, including but not limited to PII that may be contained in any video and/or another submission you upload or post to the Website (for example, your likeness). In addition, we may request information about your activities, age, interests, gender, and/or other demographic information. 

A person can choose not to supply Personally Identifiable Information, however, it is likely to affect his/her experience, and may restrict or disable access to the Website. **2\. Non-personal identification information**

We may also collect Non-personally Identifiable Information, such as IP host address, pages viewed, browser type and other data, and may aggregate any information collected in a manner which does not identify any person. 

If you visit our Website to browse, read, and/or download any information, we collect and store Non-personally Identifiable Information from you, such as, but not limited to, the name of the domain and host from which you access the Internet, the date, and time you access our Website, the Internet Protocol (IP) address of the computer you are using, and the Internet address of the website from which you linked directly to our Website. 

**3\. How we use information**

We may use the information we collect from you when you register on our Website, access the Website via social networks, or associated services available on our Website, email us, sign up for our newsletter, enter information on our Website, respond to a survey or marketing communication, surf the Website, or use certain other Website features in the following ways: 

  * To personalize User's experience and to allow us to deliver the type of content and offers in which you are most interested.
  * To improve and enhance our Website in order to better serve you, and to deliver requested Services.
  * To manage User Accounts properly, and to provide Users with customer support.
  * To allow us to better service Users in response to the customer service requests.
  * To administer a contest, promotion, survey or any other Website feature.
  * To ask for ratings and reviews of Services or the Website.
  * To communicate with Users by live chat, email or phone inquiries.
  * To verify User eligibility and deliver prizes and/or other benefits in connection with giveaways and/or Offers.
  * Perform research and analysis about your interest in and/or use of our Offers, Services, or Website content, and/or products, services or content offered by third parties.

We collect your email address in order to send various information, including information on products or services developed or provided by us, information on related products or services, news, updates, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions. If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from the mailing list, you can do that by logging into your Account and clicking the appropriate check box, or contact us by email using the contact details at the bottom of this Privacy Policy. Please note that opting out does not mean you will no longer receive emails. We reserve the right to use your email to communicate with you and to send information that you have requested. 

You should also be aware that we reserve the right to access and/or disclose Personally Identifiable Information and Non-personally Identifiable Information that we collect as required by administrative authorities and/or courts, and to the extent required to permit us to investigate suspected harassment or other violations of any law, rule, ordinance, edict, custom or regulation, the Website rules and/or policies, or the rights of third parties, or to investigate any suspected conduct we consider inappropriate or unacceptable. 

**4\. How we protect information** Maintaining the security of your Personally Identifiable Information is very important to us. We have put in place reasonable and appropriate precautions to safeguard the information we collect. However, due to the inherent open nature of the Internet, we cannot guarantee the security of your information which is stored on the Website, or the security of the communications between you and us, and you understand and agree that by continuing to use the Website you demonstrate your assumption of this risk. **5\. Cookies**

The browsers of most computers, smartphones, and other internet-enabled devices are typically set up to accept ‘cookies’. Cookies are text files that contain small amounts of information that are downloaded to your computer, or another device when you visit a website. Cookies are useful because they allow us to recognize your computer, and improve your experience on our website. Some cookies are also necessary for the technical operation of our website. You can change your cookie preferences for our website and any other website you visit using your internet browser settings. Popular internet browsers include ‘Firefox’ ‘Microsoft Explorer’ ‘Google Chrome’ and ‘Apple Safari’. The 'help' function in your browser will tell you how to do this. 

Please remember that cookies are often used to enable and improve certain functions on our Website. If you decide to switch some cookies off, it is likely to affect how the Website will work, what it will look like, and may even stop you from being able to log into a Website. 

We use cookies to store certain types of information each time you use or visit our Website. Cookies enable our system to recognize your computer, and to ensure that your User Account is attributed to the User who inputs the correct Username and Password for that Account. We (or a third party acting on our behalf) may also use cookies to display advertising appearing on our Website to you. This advertising may be served by us or by advertising partners. These cookies will not contain any personal information. Please note that this Privacy Policy is not meant to cover the use of cookies by any advertisers. 

**6\. How we share information**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your Personally Identifiable Information unless we provide Users with advance notice. This does not include website hosting partners and other parties who assist us in operating our Website, conducting our business, or serving our Users, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release information when its release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our Website policies, or protect ours or others' rights, property or safety. 

However, Non-personally Identifiable Information, visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, and/or other uses. **7\. Third party websites**

Our Website may contain links to third party websites, content, products or services that are not owned or controlled by us, and that do not operate under this Privacy Policy. We do not offer guaranties with regard to such third party websites, content, goods or services, and have no control over and assumes no responsibility for the content, privacy policies, or practices of any third party websites or services. Furthermore, our Website may include links to social networks, such as Facebook, which may afterward use information about your visit in order to target advertising to you on their websites. 

We strongly advise you to read the privacy policies of any third-party websites or services that you visit to get a clear understanding of how your Personally Identifiable Information may be collected, used, protected or otherwise handled. 

You should also be aware that any Personally Identifiable Information you voluntarily provide, post to publicly accessible sites, and transmit online may be read, collected, viewed and used by any web user. We are unable, and do not undertake, to control such uses of your Personally Identifiable Information, and you understand and agree that by using any such services you assume all the risks that the Personally Identifiable Information provided by you may be viewed and used by third parties. 

**8\. California Online Privacy Protection Act**

CalOPPA is the first state law in the USA to require commercial websites and online services to post a privacy policy. The law's reach stretches well beyond California to require a person or company in the United States (and conceivably the world) that operates websites collecting Personally identifiable information from California consumers to post a conspicuous privacy policy on its website. 

  * According to CalOPPA we agree to the following:
  * A person can visit our Website anonymously.
  * Once this Privacy Policy is created, we will add a link to it on our homepage or as a minimum on the first significant page after entering our Website.
  * Our Privacy Policy link includes the word 'Privacy' and can be easily be found on the page specified above.
  * Users will be notified of any Privacy Policy changes on our Privacy Policy page.
  * Users are able to review and change their Personally Identifiable Information by logging into their Account.

**9\. Children’s Privacy**

When it comes to the collection of personal information from children under 13, the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) puts parents in control. Our website is a general audience site, and we do not specifically market to and do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13. If you are under 13 years of age, you should not access, view or use this Website, create an account with us, and provide to us any personal information. 

**10\. Your acceptance of this Privacy Policy**

By accessing http://gamer.cash/ (the "Website") you agree to be bound by the Terms of Use, as well as this Privacy Policy which is an integral part of the Terms of Use. Please read them carefully. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO BE BOUND BY THIS PRIVACY POLICY YOU SHOULD NOT ACCESS, VIEW OR USE THIS WEBSITE. 

**11\. Modifications**

We may change the Privacy Policy at any time and we will do our utmost in informing you, though it would be prudent to review the Privacy Policy regularly yourself as your continued usage of the Website after changes mean you agree to be legally bound by the Privacy Policy as they are updated and/or amended. Any changes to the Privacy Policy will be effective immediately upon the posting of the revised Privacy Policy on this Website. 

**12\. Concluding provisions**

 **12.1.** The Privacy Policy was written in English. To the extent any translated version conflicts with the English version, the English version controls.

**12.2.** There is no expiry date for the validity of this Privacy Policy.

**12.3.** If there are any questions regarding this Privacy Policy you may contact us by email [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#51222421213e23251136303c34237f32302239).
